Hey, Kana! It's time to play!
Oh! Hi, Saekua!
Thank you for coming over to play today. I'm glad you're here.
And I'm so glad to be here, Kana!
So, uh, are we all alone? Where's your mother?
She went out shopping with Lady Toru.
So that means it's just the two of us?
Oh, my, my! What do I do?
Well, am I on my way to becoming a woman?
Are you okay?
Is this my own Cinderella story?
I think I may need to use your bathroom. Where is it?
Down and to the right.
I got the first time jitters.
Uh, um, excuse me.
The strange girl in the bathroom!
Hey, Lulu. She's a friend.
So it isn't just the two of us after all.
This is the two of us after all.
How long have you known each other?
A while, but she came here recently, and now she lives with us.
She moved in?
Now that I think about it, there are a lot of mysteries around Connor.
She always calls her mother by her last name, and she addresses the maid as lady.
Sometimes I think she's not all there, but then she says something smart.
Psycho-walk.
Are we going to play or not?
Whatever, who cares? She's still cute.
Yeah, I brought some cards with me.
Do you like cards, Alulu?
Want to play with us?
Come play.
No thanks, I'm fine.
I don't get it. Did I say something to upset her?
I lost!
It's too easy. I see it on your face.
I picked the penalty. You must rub my tummy.
This feels more like a reward!
Hey there. I just happened to be in the neighborhood, so I brought you Rugrat some snacks.
Kobayashi and Toru aren't here.
Oh, darn. I guess I'll have to stay and wait for them then.
Meanwhile, split the snacks with your friend here.
Yay!
Hey, kid.
What's wrong?
Why aren't you playing with the others?
I have no right to.
I've been evil. I tried to destroy this city.
I haven't forgiven myself yet.
Then would you like me to turn back time and make it so it never happened?
I could at least do that much for you.
No, it's fine. I know that isn't fair.
Besides, there's something Kobayashi said to me the other day that I can't stop hearing in my head.
Oh, okay, cool.
But no right to play.
Seems a little dramatic to me.
I mean, most dragons don't have the right to interact with humans.
Yet, here you are.
It's not working like it did with Miss Kobayashi.
I'll go talk to them for a bit and see what I can do.
Why don't you wait somewhere?
Yeah, there's good.
The truth is, I want to play.
I don't have to lie about those feelings anymore.
But I just don't want them to find out about what I did.
And I don't want anyone to remind Kobayashi.
It seems like she's okay as long as it's resolved.
Oh, I lost again!
Saikawa, are you losing on purpose?
No, not at all! Why would I do that?
Oh, hey, I'm bored playing cards by herself now.
I'm having so much fun with just the two of us!
Meet to pee-bee.
Pee-bee!
I gotta pee. I'll be right back.
Already?
I didn't drink any water. Why do I have to go so much?
Ah!
Um, I'm so sorry!
Um, I'm lost, sorta!
So, uh, will you tell me what your name is?
Uh, Saikawa?
Saikawa.
I, um, I actually wanted to play with you earlier.
Huh?
But I didn't think I was allowed to.
I used to be kinda violent.
How were you violent?
I tried to break all sorts of things.
Oh, so a delinquent.
I know what you think.
Violence is bad.
Hmm.
Ah, I'm actually a pretty violent person myself.
Hmm?
You mean that?
Yeah.
I tend to act out when I don't like something.
Uh-huh.
When I first met Kana, I didn't like her at all.
And I thought of many ways to strike her down.
Wow, she's...
But, um, she's way too cute to hurt,
so I decided to be friends instead.
She's so...
And to be honest, you're cute, too!
I wanna be your friend, Ilulu!
She's completely lost her mind.
Children that age shouldn't be thinking about
who they can and can't play with based on their pasts.
They're still learning to take responsibility for their faults.
Ilulu never had that opportunity where she's from.
She had to do what she was told or be forced into battle.
She had to be what the adults wanted her to be
if she wanted to fight alongside them.
Thankfully, she can let go of that here.
She has an adult who will be kind to her
and encourage her to be herself.
And if that means being an irresponsible brat
who doesn't know right from wrong, so be it.
We're home!
Hey, Lucoa, I didn't know you were here.
Sorry to make you wait.
We ran into Elma.
Shh.
Hm?
Aw.
Should I wake them up?
No.
Go grab a blanket.
I should probably call Psycho's parents.
I can feel Miss Kobayashi's eyes on my body.
She's staring right through me.
I can feel her passion burning through her side eye.
She's imagining what it would be like to look me all over.
I can tell.
If she doesn't stop, I'll just...
I'll die!
Did you sigh?
Hm?
Yeah, but not about you.
It's that maid outfit.
What?
This one?
Yeah.
I used to have one like it in high school.
I wanted to dress like a maid, too.
Used all the money from my first paycheck.
I wanted to show it off to my family.
And that's when...
What happened?
They said I looked horrible.
Everyone hated it and told me so.
Ever since then, I've embraced being an onlooker.
So, after we had that tragic conversation,
I have come up with a brilliant solution.
We should all design a new style of maid outfit
that would look cute on Miss Kobayashi.
I was hoping I could count on advice from each of you.
It's cute how desperate you become
when you think Miss Kobayashi needs something.
It means a lot to me that you could each be here today.
Alma!
What are you doing here?
No one invited you!
That's not true.
Mr. Takya invited me.
What the heck is wrong with you?
We were all coming, and I felt bad leaving her out.
It's obvious you felt guilty about it, though.
You mask your embarrassment with displaced anger.
What?
No, I don't!
Shut up!
Oh, hey.
Sorry, I didn't mean to be rude.
I guess we're having a party.
Toru must have planned this while I was napping.
You don't have to be so formal, you know.
We're your friends, too.
And I didn't think it was a party.
I just responded to a friend of mine needing help.
That's so beautiful.
Okay, Georgie, that's enough self-promotion today.
It's time to get started.
Will you please draw your ideas?
Okay.
You're so good at this, Connor.
If you buy one more property, you'll have a monopoly.
A monopoly?
Yeah, it means you're like the king of it.
You'll be able to do whatever you want with all the spaces.
Why don't you place a house in Connor's area?
Sorry about it, but this is a competition.
I don't really understand the rules,
but this game seems to bring out the worst in all of them.
Done.
That was fast.
Let's see.
When Miss Kobayashi's at work,
she's always so stoic and gets everything done as soon as possible.
So I came up with this.
What does your obsession with dessert have to do with any of this?
What? It's symbolic.
It's my favorite meal, and it makes me feel secure.
Will you please go play with the children in the other room?
I can't handle you.
Okay, see what you think of this one.
I mean, it's cute, but, like, too cute,
as in it won't look good on me.
That's awkward.
We're supposed to draw one with the idea you would wear it?
Kinda.
I'm done, too.
Where's the top?
I don't know.
Our local servants never complained when they had them on.
I'm too pasty to wear this.
Mine's done.
Okay, let's see.
Oh, thank goodness.
She's the one I'm counting on.
Here, see what you think.
Oh, thanks.
I went with the longer dress style and very minimal adornments.
She's serving classic refinement with small-town simplicity.
If I remember correctly, that's your type, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
However, we really can't define one maid outfit.
Though styles change with different eras,
the design becomes more polished every day
as the maid herself evolves in preferences and customs.
What's consistent is that it's always a maid who wears it.
It's her talent and skill that qualifies one as a maid,
not what she wears.
The maid outfit is called that
because a maid decided to wear it.
Miss Kobayashi, I am also a student.
It would be inappropriate for me to wear my maid outfit to school
or out with friends, wouldn't it?
However, just because I'm not wearing it
doesn't mean I'm not a maid.
Even if I'm wearing my school uniform,
I'm still a maid, but in a different place.
Therefore, a school uniform can actually become a maid outfit.
So, it's not what we wear.
It's what's in our hearts.
It's the spirit of service.
Quit changing the subject!
Hey, Toru.
You weren't supposed to come back.
We just finished a round.
But I'm curious.
You've been criticizing our designs.
I want to see what you came up with.
Yeah, okay, later.
That's not suspicious or anything.
Let me take off of me, you better!
Huh?
Toru, it's completely blank.
You couldn't think of anything?
It's not that.
I was just thinking I'd really like Miss Kobayashi
to wear my maid outfit.
There's no way I could do that.
Your outfit is too adorable for me.
Oh, okay.
But sure, why not?
I mean, you did go out of your way
to arrange this maid fashion focus group for me.
I'll do it.
Do you really mean that?
Okay, there.
I'm wearing it.
Oh!
You look so good!
That one looks great on you.
Please, stop.
Enough with the flattery.
I don't know how to handle it.
Let's take a photo together!
Me and you in matching maid garb.
We're like maid to Lindsay's.
If we're taking a photo, then everyone should be in it.
Ugh!
Fine!
Come on, everyone!
Get in here!
I get to be next to Miss Kobayashi!
Oh, that's not fair!
It was my idea to take it, and I was here first!
Hey, Toru?
Yes?
There's something I realized today.
And what might that be?
You remember what Georgie said?
The maid sermon?
Oh, yeah.
It's only a maid outfit because a maid wears it.
That also means, if someone wears the exact same outfit, but they're not really a maid,
then they're just a cosplayer.
Your uniform always bothered me, but after wearing it today, I had a change of heart,
embarrassing though it was.
It wasn't horrifying.
I've always liked that style and wondered what it would be like to wear one.
But I didn't think I was cute or girly enough, so I wore men's clothes instead.
I was afraid others would laugh if I wore a dress or something.
Well, now I realize that if I wanted to wear a maid outfit, I should have just worn it.
And that showed me another reality.
I wanted to be the cosplayer I always mocked.
But I could never make myself look as hot as the rest of them.
So I became an annoying maid otaku instead and obsessed about refinement and historical accuracy.
Miss Kobayashi.
I get it now.
I see you.
You work hard every day to serve as the perfect maid.
I'm sorry I called you a cosplayer.
Anything you wear can only be defined as true maid attire.
Took you long enough to realize, but at least you're being genuine.
Luckily, I still love you when you're unfair and unreasonable.
You know, I never could have said these things to you when you first came here.
Give me some credit, at least.
I appreciate everything you do around the house, Toru.
Thank you.
Me, Toru!
Why is that so hard for you to say?
Hey, this is the last bill I have.
Alolu, you're not very good with money.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure you'll pass the bank pretty soon.
And that's when you'll get some of your money back.
Okay, that's good.
But still, Shota Street is right after that.
So no matter where I stop, I'll still have to pay expensive rental fees.
There's no need to be nervous if you know what to expect.
Shut up, Root Demon!
Alolu looks chapped out.
Can you tell me if you have any hobbies?
I like being a maid.
Does that make it a hobby?
As far as free time, I have a lot of it.
What are your hobbies, Misasaki Bay?
Lately, I've been into making all kinds of delicious sweets.
Is that what that piercing noise was earlier?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Was it that loud?
Well, darn.
I still can't think of anything.
I used to love traveling.
I wonder if that would count.
Maybe music?
That's something that's popular among the humans.
Speaking of music, there's nihilistic Mr. Yana.
You said you wanted to ask me a question?
What is it?
I want to know what you find fun about music.
Probably the way it lights a fire in your soul
and makes your heart go bummer.
Makes your heart go bummer?
Go ahead and give it a try
and then I'll teach you some simple chords.
Okay.
I'm confused as to how it works.
What? Is there something wrong?
It hurts.
Your talent is so brutal.
I didn't mean to depress him.
Hi, Mr. Sone.
I just finished this one
and thought you might have a shelf to put it on.
Wow.
It came out exactly as good as the last.
You must have a lot of fun
making stuff like this, don't you?
Would you like to try one?
What do you think?
Let's see.
It is an incredibly elaborate design.
There aren't many who could make something
this advanced on their first try.
Thanks, but I still don't understand
what you find fun about it.
I tried playing some music too,
but I wasn't amused.
You know, I'm fairly certain
I happened to hear that.
It sounded to me like
you were just focusing on playing the notes
instead of making it your own.
So you could tell just by listening?
Sounded like it was too easy for you.
There was no challenge to overcome,
so no emotion was invested.
Without curiosity and emotional investment,
the hobby you choose won't be fulfilling.
Oh, is that how a hobby's supposed to work?
I'm back.
Welcome home, Kana.
Would you say that you have any hobbies?
Yeah, duh.
I like to walk on this white line.
How are you emotionally invested in this?
If I fall, I die.
I see now.
This helps her prepare for battle in limited spaces.
I did not take Kana's instincts
as a dragon seriously enough.
Oh, it stopped.
Let's keep going.
It's cool.
I'm over it now.
I mean, aren't hobbies at least supposed to be fun?
I have fun when I do it with Saikawa.
Hello, and welcome home, you two.
No fair.
Can I have one of those donuts?
Go away.
Please help me.
All you do is sleep for days.
If you don't work, then you don't eat.
Them's the rules.
How come you don't have any hobbies, Yilulu?
I do.
I'm very good at sleeping.
That's not a hobby.
That's your lifestyle choice.
Why are you so mean?
Me?
What flavor is it?
Seems like finding a hobby is hard.
Some of the kids at school like to be idols.
I heard something about that.
I'm not into singing or getting that much attention.
Ow.
I know.
That's it.
I'll get Ms. Kobayashi to become a famous idol.
We're the two.
Good work today.
Yeah, you too.
Hey, Kana, what's up?
Please come home right away.
Lady Toru's completely lost it.
She what?
What's going on?
Love kids, love kids, love kids, love kids, I love this Kobayashi.
Love kids, love kids, love kids, love kids, I love this Kobayashi, yeah.
Love the kids.
What the?
She keeps making Kobayashi merch and forcing us to like them.
She also just won't stop singing songs about you.
Kobayashi, having hobbies is so much fun.
Uh, my drinking hobby makes me act the same way, so I got nothing.
I've made the target earnings, now I just need to reach the goal.
Psycho, what are we supposed to do?
No way!
That's my Katawana!
How'd you do that?
I made a wise investment and transferred all my assets over to Kana.
You can't do that, that's cheating!
I've already given her everything else I have!
My heart, my soul, and my body!
Ah!
My beloved king!
Worship me, human.
Ah!
What's your hobby, Lucoa?
Shota, baby.
I figured. And yours is games, right, Bafnir?
Wrong.
What? It's not?
No.
Since when?
None, yeah.
This week on Who's Rotten?
Sagittarius.